Bruce Lee: The Legend is a documentary film directed by Leonard Ho.
The Official Golden Harvest tribute to the Master of
the Martial Arts Film, Bruce Lee.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by James B. Nicholson.
Self (archival), played by Bruce Lee.
Self, played by Linda Lee Cadwell.
Self, played by Raymond Chow.
Self, played by Robert Clouse.
Self, played by Nora Miao.
Leung Choi-sang (9 August 1951 – 14 January 2026), known professionally as Bruce Leung Siu-lung, was a
Hong Kong martial artist and actor who had appeared in many Hong Kong martial arts films.
Throughout his career, he often appeared billed as Bruce Leung, Bruce Liang, Bruce Leong, or Bruce Leung Siu-lung, and is thus
generally grouped among the Bruce Lee clones that sprang up after Lee's death in the subgenre known as Bruceploitation.
The film explores themes of kung fu, legend, biography, tribute.